

MEDINA DACIĆ FUKELJ

Web Developer

About Me

I am a full-stack developer with almost 5 years of experience in various technologies and frameworks.

I'm detail oriented, hard working and out of a box thinker. I'm interested only in remote contract jobs (no reallocation).

https://www.linkedin.com/in/medinadacic/



medina.daca@gmail.com



Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

LANGUAGE

- English (professional)
- Bosnian (native)

EXPERTISE

- Web development
- Angular
- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- C#
- Git
- Agile/Scrum

EXPERIENCE

Softray Solutions, Sarajevo Dec 2021 - Present (2y 7m)

I'm working as a software developer full-time job.

I mostly work with Angular, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, and C#. We use SCRUM. I also had the opportunity to work as a Mentor for new employees.

Authority Partners, Sarajevo Oct 2019 - Nov 2021 (2y 2m)

Worked as full-stack software engineer full-time job. I worked with different technologies and frameworks such as .NET, Angular, Azure, SSRS, Entity framework, Databases, SSMS, Power Bi... We used SCRUM.

EDUCATION

University of Sarajevo

Faculty of Electrical engineering, Computer Science 2015-2019

High school of Economics in Sarajevo

High School Diploma, Economics 2011-2015

PROJECTS

https://github.com/Dacili/FE-projects

My Github account: https://github.com/Dacili